[{"answer": "Hey, the key word here is tonight.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "And Don, what's the latest?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Whew.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "(On camera): When you look around at all this, what do you think, Evelyn?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Right there.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "(On camera): How did you get out?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "It was -- it was very surreal.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "It's one of the -- one of the most scary things I would imagine that you could ever be through, isn't it?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "It really is.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "I mean I -- when you've seen how many people have died, it's bordering on miraculous that nobody, given where you are on the scale of this destruction did lose their lives, isn't it?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Can you tell me what's going on in relation to that?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "We are looking at the damage in Mississippi, but particularly Alabama, you have to go back to 1974 to see this bad of a tornado outbreak.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Mr. Fugate, how bad is this and certainly in comparison to tornadoes we've seen in the past?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Well again, with this type of response, the governor of Alabama and his teams are leaving the response.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "What is the first thing that you do as a FEMA administrator to try and get to the communities that have been most hit here?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "It's been a very busy spring.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Is this a very unusual time that we are experiencing here from your experience?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "First thing is to take care of yourself and your family.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "What is the first thing they should be doing?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "There's a slight risk for some more tornadoes and severe weather on the East Coast, but the National Weather Service, their storm prediction center, kind of like the hurricane center for tornadoes, they were putting out forecasts several days ago of a risk of a moderate and then a high risk of tornadoes.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Are you expecting more?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Yes, I think about 200,000 downloads, a little more.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "And it's been going great guns, right?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "Well, I'm told that at the party --", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "What are you going to say now?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "I think -- well, firstly, you know, as you've mentioned before, you know, two bank holidays back to back with a few days of work in between and glorious sunshine is an incredible thing in England, anyway.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "How would you sum it up?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "I don't think she could have been happier, really.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "What do you think she would have made of this occasion of William's choice of bride?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I mean you've had to deal with extraordinary media scrutiny over the years.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "So I think that Diana would have been really happy that he'd found somebody with a kind of strength of character to be able to deal with the things that she couldn't deal with, you know?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "I think always to put the public's affection above the media's need for headlines, I suppose.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "What advice would you give them to living in this weird goldfish bowl?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "I think she has most people's respect in a sense even if they're not royalists, I think she has the respect of -- the fact that she's gone this long, let's be honest.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Barely put a foot wrong in that time, has she?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Well, I think, probably because there isn't that much coverage of anything on international television which is really linked strongly to the past.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Why does America go so crazy for royal events like this?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "I'd have say \"I'm Your Man\" for that.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "When we want to get things pumping at Prince Harry's disco, which of all your songs is the one that you would absolutely say is to the banker to get things going?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "\"I'm Your Man,\" I think yes.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "You think \"I'm Your Man\"?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I'm not telling you where, but I am going to a party.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Where are you going to watch?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Well, it's kind of -- I'm not sure if it's a royal wedding party or a bunch of people really taking the mick.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "A royal wedding party?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "I think the one that I put in the card, really.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "What message would you give the happy couple?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "They're the Household Cavalry, they're only a small part of it.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "All those guys on the horses looking immaculate, they're your men, right?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "As command of the Household Cavalry, I oversea the whole of the Household Recovery, all the guys on horses going out on parade.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "What would you personally be doing tomorrow on the big day?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "No, you train.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Do you get nervous or not?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "It is a huge privilege to have had him in our regiment.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "So what will you be thinking about him on the day as one of your own?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "After that, I'll be riding two inches higher in the saddle.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "You wouldn't argue with him, would you?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "We still don't know who made the dress, right?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "I'm excited about the dress.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "What are you most excited about tomorrow?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "I think the Brits, we do two things better than anybody in the world, in my opinion.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "Well, I know the Americans are fascinated with it, because I just came back from Americans and everybody was talking about it.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "What does it this mean to you as a Brit?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Because I think that they are joining the biggest reality show on Earth.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Well, allegedly, although I don't know, she loves \"Love Never Dies.\"", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "Which one is it?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "I think we really have.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Do you think we're getting a good one here?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "You wouldn't even know what Twitter is, would you?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "But you, Lord Sugar, have become my sworn enemy on Twitter.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "It's got something to do with bird song?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "I have 470,000 or something like that.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Lord?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Well, they've got to be happy on the day.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "What would you thoughts be for the happy couple?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "I hope that they have real happiness and also bringing humanity to other people, and being able to do their unique situation with a bit of joy, to be able to bring something that really lifts other people out of their own condition.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Andrew, what would your wishes for the happy couple be?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "It's a gaggle of lords.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Lords, your lordships -- what do I call you, your lordships?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Oh, I assure you, she's an amazing lady with great conversation and incredible knowledge.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Can it ever be relaxing to have dinner with the queen, her majesty, the queen?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "I think they're about the same size, except for more technology nowadays.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Any comparisons between what happened there and what's going on?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "I think he's a great young man and dearly loved by not only the people in the United Kingdom but the world.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "What kind of man is he?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Yes, we did at one of the occasions.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Have you met Kate yet?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "It's not easy.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Is it very intimidating to come into the royal family?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "It's rather extraordinary.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 638, "question": "So you're officially Serbian again?", "qSentId": 637}, {"answer": "After a few years, you become sort of vaccinated, no doubt about it.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Do they have a kind of routine, do you think, that they keep by?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "Your name is Morgan Higdin (ph)?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "Well, we had been watching the news, so we knew that there was a tornado coming, but we weren't sure where exactly it was going to hit.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Can you tell me your story?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "No, I'm on the other side.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "Can you see the building?", "qSentId": 685}, {"answer": "There was.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Any kind of warning at all though?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "I think it was probably over with in 20 seconds.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "From start to finish, how long do you think the process took?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "That's all for us tonight.", "docId": "110428pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 704}]